[{"answer": " You seen my suitcase", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " He didn't say much at all.  Honey", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What report", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Know what", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "C'mon, my friend", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Wait", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Fine.  I'm fine", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I'm not being defensive", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " What'd you say to him", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What does my friend already know", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "It's chipped", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I don't know how it can be chipped, but it's chipped", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No.  I don't think so", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Well, they're not mine", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Do you", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Save your breath.  It's not an alien spacecraft", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Time travel.  I always thought it was one of those myths... like that place's reindeer", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Maybe we didn't want to come back", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "A break for what", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": ".  We know it went through a black hole.  We saw it.  my friend", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Meaning we're never gonna get to the surface alive... to tell anyone", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You were all supposed to leave.  You weren't supposed to stay down here", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You don't understand about the sphere", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Minutes ago.  my friend's trying to decode it in his room now", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No idea.  We have no surface support. It transmitted too fast to be coming from underwater", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Where's it coming from", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Is it coming from our own computer", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You said something to me, before", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You don't remember that", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "They are or they aren't.  Which is it", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I mean, I'm not... I wasn't absolutely sure if... they", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "What?...  Wait.  Don't... why are you", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "How drastic", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I think I do", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "It's not a discharge.  Right, my friend?  You said before, right?  So it's gotta be a message", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "What's inside the sphere", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What's inside the sphere", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Yeah, I'll work on it, too", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I'm in charge", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "That's smart.  Let's talk about guns and violence", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I think we should be careful. Consider his emotional response", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "What was my friend doing outside", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "What sub", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Where did you get this", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "You went through my friend' things", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "He's not just a that place captain", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Don't tell me to calm down", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Don't do this", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "You think he killed my friend", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Bullshit.  What's out there isn't alien.  It's an animal", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Don't pull it, my friend.  It'll start a we can't stop.  my friend", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "my friend, don't do it", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Why should I go", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "In case you die, too", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "I don't trust my friend to do it", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "I fixed your suit", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": " You fixed my suit", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "But I don't know how", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": " The sub's a 100 feet in front of you.  You see it", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": " Still clear", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": " ... you there?  my friend", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": " my friend, where are you", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "What's my friend doing with your suit in there", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Fixing it?  But I fixed", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "This being after you so carefully fixed my suit", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "I don't know, my friend.  I wasn't there", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "But how", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "How can the sphere do that", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "that place's your answer", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": " that place transmission.  They're sent from that place", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": " that place transmission.  They're sent from that place", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Don't have to.  Watch.  It'll do it for you", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "It's getting cold", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "You don't think I put something in it, do you", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "You think I'd really drink that", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "You put explosives around the habitat, I can't imagine what you'd put in a drink", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "How do you feel about snakes", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "You know what I mean", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "You tell me", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "Don't you", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "No, he isn't", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "No, he can't", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "That's bullshit", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "my friend, the message said my friend. ", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Sphere.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "Hear what", "qsentId": 90}]